<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-01-22T02:30:38-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Becker Ltd</title><subtitle>CyberSec, SysAdmin, DevOps, and more.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hello, World!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/welcome" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello, World!" /><published>2021-01-18T04:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2021-01-18T04:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/welcome</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/welcome">&lt;h2 id=&quot;hello-world&quot;&gt;Hello, world!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Becker Ltd has a simple mission. Share knowledge, and provide professional and affordable services to individuals and businesses. Becker Ltd was started by &lt;a href=&quot;https://ronbecker.github.io&quot;&gt;Ron Becker&lt;/a&gt; after years of working in various fields, and gathering a large amount of knowledge and experience. He had grown tired of seeing individuals and small to medium sized businesses struggle to stay current, and keep up with big corporations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a few years of “working out the kinks” he decided it was time to start offering his skills and experience at a price that was fair, and easily manageable for all those that larger agencies had left behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“The more that you read, the more things you will know. The more that you learn, the more places you’ll go.”&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;-Dr. Seuss&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read, learn, grow, share, and see how far you can go!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ronbecker</name></author><category term="News and Updates" /><summary type="html">Hello, world! Becker Ltd has a simple mission. Share knowledge, and provide professional and affordable services to individuals and businesses. Becker Ltd was started by Ron Becker after years of working in various fields, and gathering a large amount of knowledge and experience. He had grown tired of seeing individuals and small to medium sized businesses struggle to stay current, and keep up with big corporations.</summary></entry></feed>